Here's how to spend 7 days in Iceland
away from the crowds.
>> [music]
>> Start with the classic Golden Circle and
visit the major attractions. It's a
great way to ease into Iceland.
Make sure to drop by a hot spring,
[music] an essential Iceland experience.
Get away from the crowds and head into
the highlands and drive on Iceland's
famous F-roads. These are rugged gravel
mountain roads [music] with the
occasional river crossing. Visit places
such as Kerlingarfjöll, a geothermal
valley with rising steam and colorful
mountains. Then take a dip in a natural
hot spring.
Continue to Landmannalaugar where you'll
see landscapes that almost feels like
they're from another planet.
>> [music]
>> In Landmannalaugar, make sure to go on a
hike for breathtaking views of the
surrounding area.
>> [singing]
[music]
>> Head south where you'll visit some of
Iceland's most famous sites along the
southern coast.
>> [music]
>> Visit Þórsmörk, a hidden valley
surrounded by steep green cliffs, and
hike to a viewpoint of a nearby glacier.
Next is Laki, a volcanic area with
moss-covered landscapes and large
[music] green craters. Expect several
river crossings to get there. Next visit
Skaftafell and check out the Svartifoss
waterfall.
Then continue to a viewpoint of the
Skaftafellsjökull glacier.
Go on a hike to visit this canyon with a
waterfall at the end.
>> [music]
>> End the day at the Jökulsárlón glacier
lagoon.
And on the final day, visit Vestrahorn
before making the long drive back
towards Reykjavik.
>> [music]